hi and welcome to my channel I'm Andrea
dudic with f real estate and today we're
touring this luxury custombuilt home in
the heart of Central
Texas this is a luxury home on almost 4
Acres built in
2016 it has 6,000 square ft of living
space six bed six full bath and a fourcc
car garage
[Music]
now stick with me till the end to check
out the infinity pool on a cliff let's
take a
look now as we step inside the very
first thing I noticed was this view it's
hard not to fall in love with this space
when have that kind of view there's
engineered light hardwood flooring which
really add to the open bright aesthetic
and feel of the entire
[Music]
home you're going to absolutely love the
oversized living space open concept so
that you can cook in the kitchen spend
time with your family host if you'd like
and still be connected to everyone okay
check this out this is my favorite
part Butler's
fantry and as you can see there is so
much light throughout here which is
really highlighted by the large Windows
one of my favorite features over here is
this floor to ceiling stone fireplace
with the built-in bookshelves on each
side you can really do so much with that
when decorating
[Music]
now if you saw my most recent video on
tornadoes don't be scared this home has
a safe room
[Music]
thanks so much for joining me on this
property tour today I hope you loved it
don't forget to subscribe like and click
the Bell IC so that you can stay up to
date on all things happening in Central
Texas and if you liked this tour then
follow along um soon I'll be doing a
review of a wonderful custom builder
here in Central Texas and as promised
the infinity pool
[Music]